Guide to the Washington State University Office of the President: Charles Clement French Records 1957-1966
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- 1965
  - Committees
    - Research, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 859)
    - Space priorities, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 860)
    - Ten-year planning, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 861)
    - Town and gown, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 862)
    - Traffic control, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 863)
  - Communications, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 864)
  - Compact for Education, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 865)
  - Complaints, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 866)
  - Complaints: Communist speakers, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 867)
  - Compton Union, Wilson, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 868)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 869)
  - Computing, Center, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 870)
  - Consolidated endowment fund, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 871)
  - Curriculum Advisory Program, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 872)
  - D, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 873)
  - Danforth Foundation, The, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 874)
  - Data Processing, Office of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 875)
  - Dean of Students: Work-study program, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 876)
  - E, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 877)
  - Economics and Business, College of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 878)
  - Economics and Business Research, Bureau of, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 879)
  - Education, College of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 880)
  - Electron microscope, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 881)
  - Engineering, College of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 882)
  - English, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 883)
  - Entomology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 884)
  - F, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 885)
  - Faculty, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 886)
  - Financial information: Cost Studies, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 887)
  - Financial information: Tuition and fees, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 888)
  - Fine Arts, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 889)
  - Foreign Languages, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 890)
  - Forestry and Range Management, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 891)
  - G, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 892)
  - General Extension Service, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 893)
  - General Extension Service: Project Head-Start, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 894)
  - Genetics, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 895)
  - Geology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 896)
  - Graduate Records: Office of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 897)
  - Graduate School, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 898)
  - H, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 899)
  - Hamilton Laboratory: Prosser, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 900)
  - High school summer camp, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 901)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 902)
  - Honors program, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 903)
  - Horticulture, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 904)
  - Housing and Food service, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 905)
  - I, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 906)
  - Industrial Research, Division of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 907)
  - Information, Office of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 908)
  - Institutional Research, Office of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 909)
  - Intercollegiate athletics, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 910)
  - International Programs, Office of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 911)
  - J, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 912)
  - K, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 913)
  - KWSC Radio and Television, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 914)
  - L, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 915)
  - Land acquisitions and leases, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 916)
  - Land-grant Association (Association of State Universities and Land-grant Colleges), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 917)
  - Library, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 918)
  - M, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 919)
  - Mathematics, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 920)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 921)
  - Metallurgy, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 922)
  - Military Coordinator, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 923)
  - Military Coordinator: Air Science, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 924)
  - Music Dept., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 925)
  - N, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 926)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 927)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 928)
  - National Education Association, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 929)
  - Neill, Marshall A., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 930)
  - Northwest Association of Secondary and Higher Schools, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 931)
  - Nuclear reactor, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 932)
  - O, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 933)
  - P, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 934)
  - Pakistan, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 935)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 936)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 937)
  - Physical Education for Men, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 938)
  - Physical Education for Women, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 939)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 940)
  - Placement Bureau, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 941)
  - Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 942)
  - Police Dept., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 943)
  - Police Science and Administration, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 944)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 945)
  - President's office, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 946)
  - Property inventory, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 947)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 948)
  - Publications, Office of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 949)
  - Pullman, City of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 950)
  - Pullman Herald, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 951)
  - Pullman public schools, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 952)
  - Purchasing office, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 953)
  - R, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 954)
  - Recommendations, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 955)
  - Regents, Board of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 956)
  - Registrar, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 957)
  - Registrar -- enrollment, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 958)
  - Research Corporation, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 959)
  - Research Foundation, WSU, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 960)
  - Resident instructional staff, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 961)
  - Retirement and Insurance Office, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 962)
  - Retirements, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 963)
  - Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 964)
  - S, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 965)
  - Sabbatical leaves, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 966)
  - Scholarship and development fund, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 967)
  - Scholarships, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 968)
  - Sciences and Arts, College of
    - Kennedy, T. H., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 969)
    - Ray, B. R., 1965 (Box 22, Folder 970)
  - Seattle-First National Bank, Seattle, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 971)
  - Secretarial Studies, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 972)
  - Services building -- McCluskey Hall, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 973)
  - Sigma Xi, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 974)
  - Sociology and Anthropology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 975)
  - Speech, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 976)
  - Staff personnel
    - General, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 977)
    - Personnel Committee of the Board of Regents, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 978)
  - State, Commerce and Economic Development (Technical Service Program), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 979)
  - State
    - Attorney General, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 980)
    - Auditor, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 981)
    - Census Board, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 982)
    - Central Budget Agency, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 983)
    - Civil defense, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 984)
    - General Administration, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 985)
    - Governor, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 986)
    - Governor (Governor's Council for Reorganization of State Government), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 987)
    - Governor- Higher Education Facilities Commission, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 988)
    - Legislative Council, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 989)
    - Legislature, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 990)
    - Legislature (Interim Committee on Education), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 991)
    - Legislature (Legislative Budget Committee), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 992)
    - Legislature (Temporary Advisory Council for Public Higher Education), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 993)
    - Liquor Control Board, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 994)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 995)
    - Natural Resources, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 996)
    - Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 997)
    - Public Pension Committee, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 998)
    - Senators and Representatives, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 999)
  - Student Counseling Center, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1000)
  - Student Health Service, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1001)
  - Summer session, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1002)
  - T, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1003)
  - U, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1004)
  - United States
    - A.E.C. bevation site, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1005)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1006)
    - Civil defense, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1007)
    - Defense, Dept. of (Air force), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1008)
    - Defense, Dept. of (Army), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1009)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1010)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare - research grants, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1011)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1012)
    - International Development, Agency for, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1013)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1014)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1015)
    - National Science Foundation, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1016)
    - Senators and Representatives, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1017)
    - Veterans Administration, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1018)
  - Universities and Colleges
    - Central Washington State College, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1019)
    - Eastern Washington State College, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1020)
    - Idaho, University of, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1021)
    - Miscellaneous, M-Z, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1022)
    - Washington, University of, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1023)
    - Western Washington State College, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1024)
    - 5 Institutions, Council of Presidents, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1025)
  - V, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1026)
  - Veterinary Medicine, College of, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1027)
  - Vice president
    - Academic, Academic report, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1028)
    - Academic, Office of, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1029)
    - Business, Bond, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1030)
    - Business, Office of, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1031)
    - Business, Vending machine, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1032)
  - W, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1033)
  - Washington State Grange, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1034)
  - Water Research Resources Center, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1035)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1036)
  - Wildlife research unit, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1037)
  - X-Y-Z, 1865, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1038)
  - YMCA and YWCA, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1039)
  - Zoology, Dept. of, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1040)
- 1966
  - A, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1041)
  - Administrative Council, Dept. Chairmen, Supts., Supervisors, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1042)
  - Admissions, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1043)
  - Admissions, Community colleges, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1044)
  - Advisory Boards, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1045)
  - Agricultural Chemistry, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1046)
  - Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1047)
  - Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1048)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1049)
  - Agriculture, Resident instruction, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1050)
  - Agriculture - Cooperative Extension Service, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1051)
  - Agriculture - Cooperative Extension Service, 4-H clubs, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1052)
  - Agriculture research
    - Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1053)
    - Office of Director, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1054)
    - Tree Fruit Research Center, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1055)
    - Western Washington Research and Extension Center, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1056)
  - Agronomy, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1057)
  - American Assembly, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1058)
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education (AACTE), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1059)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1060)
  - American Association of University Women, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1061)
  - American Council on Education, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1062)
  - Animal Sciences, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1063)
  - Anthropology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1064)
  - Applications, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1065)
  - Architect, University, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1066)
  - Architect, University: Space analyst, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1067)
  - Architecture, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1068)
  - ASWSU, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1069)
  - ASWSU - bonds, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1070)
  - ASWSU - publications, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1071)
  - Athletic Association of Western Universities, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1072)
  - Audio-visual Center, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1073)
  - B, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1074)
  - Bacteriology and Public Health, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1075)
  - Biology, General, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1076)
  - Botany, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1077)
  - Budget office, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1078)
  - Building names, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1079)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1080)
  - Business Administration, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1081)
  - C, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1082)
  - Chamber of Commerce: Pullman, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1083)
  - Spokane, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1084)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1085)
  - Chemical Engineering, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1086)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1087)
  - Civil Engineering, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1088)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1089)
  - Committees
    - Academic program, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1090)
    - Academic standing, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1091)
    - Catalog subcommittee of EPC, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1092)
    - Commencement, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1093)
    - Committee on committees, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1094)
    - Educational policies, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1095)
    - Faculty executive, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1096)
    - Graduate studies, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1097)
    - Lecture artist series, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1098)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1099)
    - Patent, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1100)
    - Research, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1101)
    - Space priorities, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1102)
    - Ten-year planning, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1103)
    - Town and gown, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1104)
    - Traffic control, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1105)
    - Undergraduate scholarships and student aids, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1106)
  - Communications, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1107)
  - Compact for education, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1108)
  - Comparative behavior laboratory (Primate center), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1109)
  - Complaints, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1110)
  - Compton Union, Wilson, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1111)
  - Computing Center, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1112)
  - Controller, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1113)
  - Consolidated endowment fund, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1114)
  - Curriculum Advisory Program, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1115)
  - D, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1116)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1117)
  - Data Processing, Office of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1118)
  - Dean of Students, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1119)
  - Dean of Students -- Work study program, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1120)
  - E, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1121)
  - Economic and Business Research, Bureau of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1122)
  - Economic and Business, College of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1123)
  - Education, College of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1124)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1125)
  - Electrical Engineering, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1126)
  - Engineering, College of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1127)
  - Engineering research, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1128)
  - English, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1129)
  - Entomology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1130)
  - F, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1131)
  - Financial information -- General, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1132)
  - Financial information -- Salary schedules, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1133)
  - Fine Arts, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1134)
  - Forestry and Range management, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1135)
  - Foreign Languages, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1136)
  - G, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1137)
  - General Extension Service, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1138)
  - General reserve, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1139)
  - Genetics, Program in, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1140)
  - Graduate School, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1141)
  - H, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1142)
  - High school summer camp, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1143)
  - History, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1144)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1145)
  - Honors program, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1146)
  - Horticulture, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1147)
  - Housing and Food Service, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1148)
  - Housing and Food Service (bonds), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1149)
  - I, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1150)
  - Information, Office of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1151)
  - Institutional Research, Office of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1152)
  - Intercollegiate athletics, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1153)
  - International programs, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1154)
  - J, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1155)
  - K, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1156)
  - Kimborough Hall -- Music building, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1157)
  - KWSC, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1158)
  - Land acquisitions, leases, etc., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1159)
  - Land-grant Association (National Association of State Universities and Land-grant Colleges), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1160)
  - Library, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1161)
  - M, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1162)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1163)
  - Military Coordinator, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1164)
  - Military Coordinator -- Military Science, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1165)
  - Music, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1166)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1167)
  - Neill, Marshall A., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1168)
  - Northwest Association of Secondary and Higher Schools, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1169)
  - Nuclear reactor, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1170)
  - O, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1171)
  - Old National Bank, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1172)
  - P, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1173)
  - Pakistan, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1174)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1175)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1176)
  - Physical Education for Men, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1177)
  - Physical Education for Women, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1178)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1179)
  - Placement Bureau, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1180)
  - Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1181)
  - Police Dept., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1182)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1183)
  - Pre-nursing, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1184)
  - President's office, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1185)
  - Property inventory, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1186)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1187)
  - Publications, Office of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1188)
  - Purchasing office, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1189)
  - R, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1190)
  - Recommendations, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1191)
  - Regents, Board of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1192)
  - Registrar, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1193)
  - Registrar -- enrollment, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1194)
  - Research Corporation, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1195)
  - Research Foundation, WSU, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1196)
  - Resident instructional staff, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1197)
  - Retirement and insurance office, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1198)
  - Retirements, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1199)
  - Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1200)
  - S, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1201)
  - Sabbatical leaves, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1202)
  - Scholarship and development fund, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1203)
  - Scholarships, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1204)
  - Sciences and Arts, College of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1205)
  - Sciences and Arts, College of
    - Kennedy, T. H., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1206)
    - Ray, B. Roger, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1207)
  - Seattle-First National Bank, Seattle, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1208)
  - Sigma Xi, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1209)
  - Sociology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1210)
  - Speech, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1211)
  - Staff personnel
    - General, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1212)
    - Personnel committee of the Board of Regents, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1213)
  - State
    - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1214)
    - Attorney General, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1215)
    - Auditor, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1216)
    - Commerce and Economic Development (Technical Service Program), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1217)
    - Census Board, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1218-1219)
    - Central Budget Agency, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1220)
    - General Administration, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1221)
    - Governor -- Governor's Council for Reorganization of State Government, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1222)
    - Governor -- Prior report, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1223)
    - Legislative council, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1224)
    - Legislature (Legislative Budget Committee), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1225)
    - Legislature (Temporary Advisory Council for Public Higher Education), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1226)
    - Legislature -- Temporary Advisory Council (Site brochures) (Temporary), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1227)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1228)
    - Treasurer, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1229)
  - Summer session, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1230)
  - U, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1231)
  - U.S.
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1232)
    - Defense, Dept. of (Army), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 1233)
    - Health, Education, Welfare (All branches), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1234)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1235)
    - Interior, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1236)
    - Interior, Dept. of (BPA advisory council), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1237)
    - International Development, Agency for, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1238)
    - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1239)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1240)
    - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1241)
    - National Science Foundation, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1242)
    - President, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1243)
    - Senators and Representatives, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1244)
    - Treasury Dept., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1245)
    - Veterans Administration, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1246)
  - Universities and Colleges
    - Central Washington State College, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1247)
    - Eastern Washington State College, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1248)
    - Idaho, University of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1249)
    - Miscellaneous, A-L, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1250)
    - Miscellaneous, M-Z, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1251)
    - Oregon, University of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1252)
    - State community colleges, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1253)
    - Washington, University of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1254)
    - Washington College Association, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1255)
    - Washington State University, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1256)
    - Western Washington State College, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1257)
    - 5 Institutions
      - Council of Presidents, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1258)
      - Northwest Interinstitutional Council on Study Abroad, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1259)
      - Other interinstitutional committees, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1260)
  - Veterinary Medicine, College of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1261)
  - Vice president
    - Academic, Academic reports, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1262)
    - Academic, Small classes, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1263)
    - Academic, Office of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1264)
    - Business, Office of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1265)
    - Finance, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1266)
    - Finance (Bonds), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1267-1268)
  - W, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1269)
  - Washington Education Association, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1270)
  - Water -- Moscow-Pullman study, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1271)
  - Water Research Resources Center, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1272)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1273)
  - Wildlife research unit, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1274)
  - X-Y-Z, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1275)
  - Zoology, Dept. of, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1276)